When I was a kid, I used to ride on the
Toshimaya train.
I remember that the staff who worked
there were smiling and saying,
Then we will smile too.
I can't do it!
I remember that the staff and children
were smiling and talking.
Yes.
I'm glad.
Rock on to your heart! We are Super
Exciting Advertising Club!
This time is the last special supporter
for Super Exciting Advertising Club
Toshimayen!
Special anniversary!
Today, we will send it from Toshimayen!
I'm so excited!
Thank you!
Uh皮毛さんのタイガナッセフェラーサッポーターリーなんだ
調べていた
Thank you for watching!
Thank you so much for having us.
This program is a program in which six
people who are active to promote
something exciting challenge various
things and promote the excitement and
entertainment in the world.
I will prove it to you.
What kind of things will you do as a
special supporter?
Let's go in order.
First, the second one.
Thank you for watching.
It's the Zacca freeze ad in lab香 seige!
It's amazing!
Don't miss it.
Please check it too!
Here it is.
that I would like to to chew
No!
At the station, Saimeiji, Seibu,
Ikebukuro, Seibu, Shinjuku,
What was it?
The special supporter called us to
watch the video.
I think you'll be able to see it.
If you're lucky, you'll be able to see
it.
Everyone, please watch it.
Please watch it.
Next is smilevision Tource Operation's
Kizuna Gensei Smilevision,
That's all!
Smile Vision
Yes, it's on the train
Wow
So when you get on the train
You can see it
Not on your phone
Please watch it
Thank you
Ennai Poster
Ennai, a year ago
Please watch it
Please watch it.
It was cute.
Yes.
Please watch it.
The last one is
Code page special page.
Yeah!
Please watch it.
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
Please take care of us!
The last one is the most important one,
right?
Yes!
Let's go!
Special supporter!
We'll do our best!
The most important!
Please check it out!
Let's go! Tumo Tumo Tumorou! Saikyo
Set!
Hello! Hello! To the new me!
It doesn't matter what they say!
Let's go back to the past and
challenge!
Tumo Tumo Tumorou! Saikyo Set!
Hello! Hello! To the infinite
possibilities!
So, this time, we have a staff member
from a year ago with us!
Yay!
Where is she?
Where are you?
Wow!
She is moving!
Maybe?
She is too fast.
Wow!
She is having fun!
I want to fly!
We want to fly too!
I am wearing red.
She is moving!
Please subscribe to our channel!
I'm going to cry.
I didn't expect this.
I can't say anything.
This time, we had a staff member,
Komine, come to the event.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I was impressed by your entrance.
You made a pose.
I won't stand up at the end.
I see.
Don't imitate Yui.
She is on the stage now.
Let's ask questions to them.
Let's ask them.
Why did you choose the Super Special
Advertisement for the Special Supporter?
Well, it's a year before the year that
will be a milestone in the history of
the 94 years.
It's a little sad, isn't it?
It's sad, but I want to end with a
smile.
I want to end with a smile.
And I want you to advertise the last of
the year.
Advertisement.
Super Special Advertisement.
Wow!
I didn't know that such a special name
would come out.
Thank you very much.
It's a little funny.
I thought it was a good name for the
Super Special Advertisement.
It was a good idea.
Thank you very much.
I have to advertise it.
I'll do my best.
This year is the 94th anniversary of
the history of the 94 years.
What do you think of the year before
the year?
There are good things and bad things.
There are only good things.
I remember seeing a lot of children's
smiles.
Not only me, but also the staff who
work at the amusement park and move the
rides,
they work to see the children's smiles.
I remember seeing the staff and
children talking with smiles.
I remember seeing a lot of children's
smiles.
Before I got on the train, they were
waving to me with a smile.
They were talking to me.
I felt that I could smile with that.
I realized that we are doing this with
that kind of feeling.
The staff's smile is also very...
Yes, yes, yes.
I can feel the kindness of people.
Maybe that's because the staff was
riding on the train to Toshima when they
were children,
and the staff who worked at that time
were smiling,
so I think we have a feeling of saying
with a smile.
I can't do it!
I think the staff will be happy if you
say it.
I really felt it.
I think it's warm when people come to
Toshima.
Thank you very much.
Next, I will talk about me.
I'm from Toshima Island. I like go-
karts and roller coasters.
I wanted to go to this attraction when
I came to Toshima Island.
I like go-karts and roller coasters.
My favorite is...
The Merlion.
It's beautiful.
It's made of wood.
It's a warm vehicle.
The design is very detailed.
It's a vehicle with a history of 113
years.
I would like to recommend this place to
everyone.
Thank you for watching.
We can take a lot of pictures.
I'm happy.
This is the third floor.
The interior design is fast.
If you like fast things, you can choose
the interior design.
Everything is cute.
The interior design is fast.
There is a horse with bangs.
You know it well.
I know it recently.
It's really embarrassing.
I said it's a lie.
But it's true.
Horse's hair is real horse's hair.
Is it the tail?
Yes.
You touched it.
It's smooth.
I'll ask the last question.
Why did you decide to work at
Toshimayan?
I'm 38 years old.
I came to Toshimayan when I was a
child.
I was close to Toshimayan when I was in
kindergarten.
I came to Toshimayan after I finished
I came here every day.
I came to Toshimayan when I was a
child.
I came to Toshimayan when I grew up.
It's amazing.
You have a lot of memories.
I met my first love when I came here.
You are playing the heart shaker of
youth.
I went to a haunted house.
It's amazing.
I was scared and ran away.
A girl doesn't run away.
You have a lot of memories.
It's a place where I have a lot of
memories.
I felt it just by listening to your
story.
I'm grateful to such an important
place.
On the contrary, we are grateful.
You have a lot of music videos.
I think you like it.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Thank you very much.
We are a super-enthusiastic publicity
team.
We are special supporters.
We will do our best.
Let's go! Tumo Tumo Tumorou! The
strongest!
Hello! Hello! To the new me!
It doesn't matter what they say!
Let's attack more fiercely!
Tumo Tumo Tumorou! The strongest!
Hello! Hello! To the infinite
possibilities!
Okay, now it's time for the
announcement segment!
Yay!
Thank you for watching!
Please cheer up.
What is today's theme?
Today's theme is Kanami.
Kanami's theme is this.
The first person is this.
Priority is important.
It's important.
It's very important.
I'll show you.
Our favorite advertising team, New
Chara Paburin is now in the New Chara
Grand Prix.
Please vote for us.
All members are voting.
U-chan and Karu-chan are also
supporting us.
I'll do my best.
Ojuri is this.
What is this?
This is a wonderful picture drawn by
Haruka Koizumi.
Please laugh when you see this picture.
What is this picture?
What is this?
I didn't know.
Let's move on.
This is this.
Thank you.
Next, we will be having a live
performance of Super Excited Hito-chan's
Birthday!
This is on Saturday, July 25th, 2020,
and it's my birthday!
I'm 19 years old, so please celebrate
my 19th birthday with me!
Next, I'm going to hold a live concert
of the Hiori's Birthday Party!
This will be held on August 8th, 2020!
I'm 19 years old, so please celebrate
my 19th birthday with me!
Next, I'm going to hold a live concert
of the Hiori's Birthday Party!
I'm 19 years old, so please celebrate
my 19th birthday with me!
I'm going to hold a live concert of the
Hiori's Birthday Party!
This will be held on August 22nd, 2020
and 23rd, Tuesdays!
This will be held at Hachikawa Arena!
It's 360 degrees in the middle of the
stage, so everyone can see everything
from the side and behind!
Please come and enjoy the concert!
I'm going to hold a live concert of the
Hiori's Birthday Party!
It's different!
Everyone, it's different!
It's the first Kanamin!
Is it okay?
No, no, no!
Are you going to do it here?
It was over there, wasn't it?
The super exciting Kanamin's Birthday
Party will be held at an audience-free
live!
The date is July 24th, 2020!
The day is the basis of the CD, and we
will hold a series of birthday parties
for two consecutive days, so it will be
a 21-year-old Kanamin's birthday party!
Please come and see!
I was more excited when I was in the
U-KERJU ANTHEM!
Certainly!
Is it better to come out?
Please announce this properly!
This is the first live after the new
formation of Super Exciting Channel!
The Super Exciting Coaster that leads
to the future of Super Exciting Channel
will be held on July 18th!
It's only three days left!
We will hold a free live broadcast on
July 18th!
It's a free broadcast, so please come
and see!
Please come and see!
We've done everything!
We've done it!
There was one extra thing in there.
I don't need it.
I'm not going to use it.
How long are you going to use this?
It was good.
Can I make a T-shirt with this?
A T-shirt for Christmas!
Stop it!
We have 3 days left until the live
stream of Z!PANDAL!
It will be on Amex and Toki's YouTube
channel.
Please come and see us!
subs by maro!
It's just the right amount of fun to be
able to be loved
We can't help but sing, we can!
I want the strongest again!
Oh no!
Tumor, tumor, tumor, the strongest
Hello, hello to this wonderful world
It doesn't matter how difficult the
story is
Just being alive is exciting
Tumor, tumor, tumor, the strongest
Hello, hello to this unexpected
encounter
Let's live with a smile for now
Thank you, both sweet and sour
Happy friendship!
Let's charge our power together!
Let's all clap our hands together!
If we all work together
We'll shout out with super full power!
Energy! Max!
Motivation! Max!
Courage! Max!
Enthusiasm! Max!
Friendship! Max!
Affection! Max!
Enthusiasm! Max!
It feels good!
Please subscribe to our channel and
follow us on Twitter!
subs by maro!
It's supposed to be fun, right?
Right?
Yes, we are the last special supporter
of the Super Tokimeki Promotion Club
Toshimae-san.
We will do our best to liven up
Toshimae-san, so please take care of us.
Please take care of us.
Everyone, please liven up together.
Thank you!
I'll do everything I want to do
I'll prove my exciting future
Happy New Day!
Go! Go! Tomorrow!
Let's go! Tomorrow! Let's be the
strongest!
Go! Go! Tomorrow!
Let's go! Tomorrow! Let's be the
strongest!
Go! Go! Tomorrow! Let's be the